Who the hell are you guys?
Look, this is a private party, so get lost!
We're only here to talk.
Would you please leave this town?
Been a long time since we heard that line.
Thank you.
You can fly away
The world is going to shine
Ley me up to see you
Please use my angel at the top and put it
It is the starting to take up
何度でも立ち上がれ
lek atau...
西からはあなた representing上がる
何かによataがとても日本見つけられる
招くこの靴が殺我
中の割のときに
招きま going to burn you out of the ring
整体はどう?
僕はルーズターキで millimeters
その人がいい
巨大剣
That long to produce so little, Wren.
I'll admit, you're stronger than I thought.
Let me go! I give up, I lose! Just let me go!
He said he lost already! Why didn't you let him go?
He knew what the rules are. You lose if you step outside the ring.
Anything else, including a forfeit, is completely meaningless.
You kicked me, then stepped outside the ring too. So you lost as well.
Oh no! Hold on a second! Let's start over!
Don't bother, Gon. You're probably eager to try out your big ultimate move.
But hold off. Not in front of all these people. Here, I'll handle it.
What's this? Are you gonna team up on me?
Let me borrow this.
Huh?
You wouldn't!
Well, guess I win.
You brat! You're dead!
Huh?
You made up all of the rules yourself. So get over it.
Yeah, that's on me. This way. I'll take you to the boss.
Huh? This is where your boss is?
Got visitors, boss.
Yeah, and who are they?
Seems they want us to leave town.
That's so.
Then let's have a contest, shall we?
If you win, we'll leave the island peacefully.
It'll be up to us to choose what the contest will be.
Alright?
And what if we lose? What'll happen to us then?
Oh, nothing really.
You'll just have to leave instead. Simple as that.
Fine. Let's go.
It's an athletics contest.
Where each member will challenge you to a match in their specialty sport.
One win each.
First to eight wins is the victor.
My challenge is first up. Then I'm gonna go with boxing.
Well? Who wants to take him?
I've got this one.
There is just one special condition.
You can use items conjured by Nen.
What the hell? You can't call that boxing!
Don't worry about it. I'm just gonna use my fist.
That rule is only for your benefit.
Tag out if you want to.
That's not gonna happen.
Fight!
I know what's going on here.
But I figure if you choose boxing, there must be a reason!
You're an emitter too, aren't you? We're fighting in close proximity. And this? Well, this is a finite space. Making it an ideal situation for an emitter.
But you made one mistake! Not anticipating that I might be stronger than you!
Wow! He can't dodge that speed!
Yes, he's down! That was easy!
No, they were both hit. Huh?
What in the hell just happened? How?
These guys really didn't see that?
Their guy teleported.
Wait, what do you mean?
Just his fist, a short uppercut.
From the very start, his goal was to land a knockout counter.
I thought it was pretty obvious.
Hmm.
Seems he's out cold. That looks like a win for our side.
Damn.
...
Ugh!
Damn.
Eight wins with them will be impossible.
Which means...
Now, for the next challenge,
we're juggling soccer balls.
Okay, I'm up.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
All right.
That would be quite wise indeed.
Hmm.
Hi, this round is you and me.
A little girl, huh?
I guess I'll have to be real careful not to injure you.
Injure me with juggling?
Hmm.
We're both allowed to attack using our Nen,
if you don't touch the ball with your hands.
Yes, I get it.
Moving is allowed anywhere inside the building,
and whoever drops the ball first loses.
Right.
I understand.
Okay.
Then let's get started.
Ready?
Go!
Oh, goodness.
That was much harder than I expected.
I guess I lose.
I'm next, big guy.
Do you want to go?
Yeah, you think?
You are so gonna get it.
Ready?
And fight!
I'll squash you like a bug!
Oh, sorry.
I stepped outside the rain.
Okay.
I think I see what they're up to.
That's eight wins for us.
So we're the victors.
Go on, get out of here.
We'll keep doing whatever we want in this town.
Where are you going, you little snot?
Fight me again!
You knew we couldn't win with this lineup, so you threw it and totally focused on gathering
information.
But once a party has been defeated, there are no second chances.
It's all right.
We just need to switch out one member, so it was well worth the risk.
Our team's dropping out.
Huh?
We fulfilled our original objective, preventing the bomber from winning the game.
It'll be impossible for them to assemble a group of 15 players.
You should give up on this contest for a bit.
If you do get the card, you'll just become targets.
Those guys just don't get it.
Our strategy.
It makes sense to obtain this card as fast as we can.
Right.
In order to reduce the chances of fighting within the group.
Exactly.
Huh?
You need at least 15 people to participate.
Even if you use clone, you can only obtain three copies of Strip of Beach.
Looks to me like this event was specially designed to incite infighting.
That's what you were talking about before, wasn't it?
Well, that's pretty brutal.
Of course.
I didn't understand it right away.
Assuming that the four of us are capable of winning, we need four more with us who are
up to the task.
In a perfect world, they would already be in a group of 11.
Do you have any leads?
Now, Buk, going by the names on my list, it looks like Chrollo's probably the strongest.
But Kurapika told me that the Chrollo here is definitely an imposter.
So who do you think it is then?
Well, probably a member of the troop.
But why would a member of the troop be here?
Not sure.
Maybe to beat the game?
Well then why wouldn't they want to use their own name?
I have no idea.
Try using Clairvoyance.
If this person didn't come all the way here to beat the game, they simply wouldn't bother
collecting cards.
Yeah, you're right.
Wow, this guy isn't even trying.
Looks like the only cards he's obtained are for food and water.
Actually, that can make it a lot easier to invite them.
But if it really is a member of the troop, we won't invite them.
We'll see what they say.
Yeah?
What's the point of even trying?
We already know it's one of them.
We need to know who they are, but why they're here is more important.
What are you, a damn idiot?
Are you just going to ask them why they're here?
Because big surprise, they're not going to tell you.
Yeah, I'm an idiot, fine, but I'm still going to ask and you can't stop me.
Then go right ahead.
Great.
Maybe I will.
Are they okay?
This kind of thing happens every day.
I'm going.
Then quit yapping and just do it.
Accompany on!
Crawl a low silver!
Then quit yapping and just do it!
Accompany on!
Crawl a low silver!
The next part is to make it look always possible so you can watch a time, but it is okay...
No way.
Hisoka!
Hmm.
What have we here?
It seems I have unexpected guests.
Long time no see.
Just as I suspected.
You've matured quite a lot, haven't you?
You've clearly found an excellent teacher.
You'll continue to ripen into sweet fruit, just as I thought.
Okay, so do you guys actually know this, pervert?
Ah, you must be their teacher, I assume.
No, doesn't seem the type.
Ah! Oh no! Oh my gosh!
It's her.
What do you want with me, or perhaps more accurately with Chrollo?
I have a question.
What are you doing in the game?
Well, what to do now?
Well, if I talk, I know how they'll react.
They'll do everything in their power to keep the spiders from the Nen Exorcist.
That could be interesting in and of itself, but I don't want to delay my fight with Chrollo any longer than I have to.
I came here to look for Chrollo.
He's still crippled by Kurapika's Nen, but there's actually a way to remove it.
Exorcism.
You knew?
Well, that will make this much easier.
I'm looking for Chrollo to pass that along, but I have no leads.
Before long, I remembered that some of the spiders were interested in this game.
So, of course, if I can locate them, they might be able to tell me where Chrollo is.
And using his handle, all but guarantees they'll try to contact me.
Okay. So he was just pretending to be a member of the Phantom Troop.
Yeah.
Now, I have a question for you.
Tell me, did the two of you really come all the way out here just to ask me that?
Yeah, sure did.
Um...
The truth is, we're here looking for people who are really strong.
And we were hoping you might join us.
Huh? All right.
May I ask why you're looking for strong people?
Hey, wait a minute. I don't think I like this. It's risky.
It sure is. You don't know who this guy is, risky.
What? Of course I know who he is.
Not personally, but I feel a certain kinship with him.
The city of love, Ai-Ai, isn't very far from here.
You can meet all kinds of people. You might even find the strength that you're looking for.
What exactly did you mean about him lying?
Well, technically, I should have said that he wasn't telling the truth.
But how could you tell?
It was really more of a hunch.
Seriously?
After lying for 50 years myself, I can recognize a fellow liar.
That's actually pretty convincing.
It's obvious he's hiding something, so best to keep him around until we can find out what.
Plus, he's really strong, isn't he?
Yeah.
Hey, Hisoka! You walk in front!
Ten more members.
That's what we need, correct?
Yeah. Members like you. People who have little or no interest in cards.
I would have thought everyone else was here to beat the game.
I doubt there are many other eccentrics like myself.
Oh, he's hiding something. I can feel it.
By the way, did you use someone's power to fly over here by any chance?
It's a spell. The game is full of them.
Oh, so that's what it was.
You need to buy spells from stores, yes?
Something doesn't make sense.
If he isn't being honest with us,
there must be some kind of inconsistency in his words.
He says he only came here to find spiders
who might know where to find Chrollo.
There's got to be a clue in there somewhere.
Oh no! Where are my glasses?
Get them for her.
You might become friends.
Excuse me!
You should watch where you're going!
Be more careful!
Sorry!
I'm gonna be late!
Why did you apologize?
What you should have done is told her to watch where she was going,
starting an argument.
Stop it! Please!
Let me go!
I swear I'll scream!
Fine! Scream your heart out!
Not like anybody's gonna save you.
Hold it right there!
Huh?
You let her go right now!
Hey, that hurt!
What are you doing falling for such a tired old cliché, huh?
Really? You want me to be your hair model?
You're hair's so long and lovely, it would be my honor to style it.
Yes!
There's no point in us hanging around this stupid city.
Hisoka, let's go somewhere else.
But why?
At least here, boredom isn't an issue.
Boredom?
That's it.
That's what didn't click earlier.
It's this place that's the problem.
If I entered this game just to hunt someone down,
what would I do?
First, I'd see how important the spell cards are.
Gon and Bisuki ran into Hisoka while I was outside,
retaking the hunter exam.
That must have been while they were training near Masadora.
He was in Masadora!
Normally, it wouldn't make sense for him to leave.
Most players pass through there looking for spell cards.
If he really was looking for the troop,
he wouldn't have left.
At least here, boredom isn't an issue.
He's bored because he's got nothing to do.
So he isn't looking for anyone.
No.
He's already found them.
That's it.
That's in line with what Bisuki was saying earlier.
Hisoka already met up with the troop.
Now he's waiting for something.
But what?
What else could...
An exorcist!
The exorcist is here on Great Island!
Hisoka and the troop already know that.
I can't tell Gon about it yet.
He's a terrible liar.
If Hisoka finds out we know,
he's bound to slip away from us.
If he leaves,
we'll be down an ally
and we won't know what the troop is doing.
We can't let that happen.
Hey, Killua?
I've been thinking.
Tetsugera.
We should probably try to recruit him.
Even if he won't join,
we should at least meet him.
And that way,
he'll be on our binder list.
Yeah, it'd be better if we knew
what they were up to.
The binder?
We can find out for sure.
Can I see your binder, Hisoka?
We're trying to find a guy named Tetsugera,
so I want to see if he's on the list
of players you've met.
List?
This is perfect.
If I started asking a bunch of questions,
Hisoka would get suspicious.
But since Gon doesn't know anything,
Hisoka won't see a problem with it.
Book.
If he refuses to show us the screen,
that'll just support my theory.
There he is, Tetsugera.
Really?
Yes, look, here.
He's showing us?
No way.
It doesn't look like there are
any troop members listed.
Was I being paranoid?
Could Hisoka actually still be looking for them?
Hmm.
In that case,
would you recite the spell?
Don't worry.
We'll do all the talking.
Contact on, Tetsugera.
My texture surprise certainly does come in handy.
Hisoka's ability completely fools Killua and his friends.
But the question remains,
is he friend or foe?
Sometimes the limitation safe...
That it isn't for you to,
but to be capable of doing Origin.
Do you think?
learning
doesn't make any sound
igh
much
Get
E
We don't
going
long
it's
super
big
X
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある
だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ 早いだろ
身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの 手放したとき 始まる何か
上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて 感じるリズム そう僕らのやり方で
つまりではない時間 ありがとうございます
今まで1時2時間  sweepたくなりして5時間 で
5時間くらいは骨折でき つまり Meter ¿かわっつーとなかなか
茹んで慶ん sem bırakに沸いて塗れるもの しょうか
ラバジャーも入ってされた ゆき sulfurっぽいんだけど
Lorさんは家族 municipalの改革があって議養を買って
こちらの中を仕上げるような状態になる